I've got a new comic for sale!
I'd like one copy, please!
Of course. Here you are.
Thanks for your support!
Expo!!
It doesn't look quite right...
Sakura? The bathroom's free.
Give me a minute. I need to—
No, now. Hurry up and take a bath.
Fine.
A swordswoman...
It's hard to picture in my mind.
Maybe I'm bad at drawing strong women...
Hm...
She's got a nice figure...
she's driven, and she follows her heart...
That might work!
Perfect!
Cosplay...?
Vendors...?
Um, yeah.
I'll be attending an event soon,
but I was hoping you two could
help me out with it...
What kind of event?
Uh...
H-Here.
Manga?
It's called "doujinshi."
I drew it.
Whoa, no way! It's so good!
This art is fantastic!
Mochida, I had no idea you were so talented!
Thanks.
But, um... maybe don't look at it so closely.
I've loved anime and manga since I was little,
and I've been selling comics at these
types of events for quite some time now.
Huh, I didn't know that was a thing.
Sounds like fun—
I know, right?!
I love walking into the venue and
feeling the enthusiasm in the air!
I wanted my latest comic to be
a classic fantasy story,
and I based the daring swordswoman on you,
Bell, so if you work the booth—
M-Mochida...
Oh, sorry...
I don't know much about this stuff...
but since you asked, sure.
Y'mean it?!
Yeah...
You're in, right, Hinata?
Sure am. We'd be happy to help you out.
Thank you!
Um, in that case...
are you free after school today?
Ooh...
So this is what your room looks like.
Cute!
Sunohara's in my room...!
I'm assuming we can't buy the costumes.
Yeah, it's an original design.
After I take your measurements,
I can ask a friend of mine to make it.
I'll probably make the accessories myself.
Still not done with my manuscript, though...
Then don't stress yourself out.
We can wear normal—
No!
Since you two are helping me,
the costumes are non-negotiable!
Alright, let's start with your measurements, Bell!
Okey-dokey!
Wha—? Hinata!
You didn't have to take off your underwear...
Okay, I'm going to get
your measurements now.
You're kidding me...
Huh?
Uh, sorry. On to the next one.
Bell, you really do have a great figure.
Think so?
I bet Sunohara prefers her body type over mine...
Sakura?
Huh?
Oh, don't give me that.
You're going to cosplay with us, right?
N-No, I'm good!
I just wanted the two of you to do it.
What are you talking about?
You're the star of the event,
so you have to dress up, too!
B-But...
I see what's happening.
Forcing me and Hinata to do all the work
while you sit back and enjoy yourself...
How cruel! It's totally unfair!
Okay, fine.
Heh.
Now hurry up and take your clothes off.
Wha—? Bell...?!
Don't put up a fight!
Wait, Bell! Hold on!
There's nowhere left to run!
Now then, I think it's time we measure
every square inch of you!
N-No, stop!
Are they okay in there...?
Whew!
I guess it's Hinata's turn next.
Hinata!
B-Bell...?
We're done with our measurements.
I'll go ahead and take yours now.
At least put on some clothes first!
It's huge!
Wow! I didn't realize the event venue
would be so big!
Check-in's over there.
There'll be a dressing room once we're inside,
so we can get changed in there.
Dressing Room Check-in
Well? What do you think?
You look adorable!
It's a perfect reproduction!
I asked my friend to make
the bust portion pretty big,
but it still accentuates all the right places!
Oh no, I think I might be falling in love
with my own character!
Thanks. You look cute, too.
No way! You look way cuter than I do, Bell!
Uh, Mochida?
Doesn't my costume seem a little... feminine?
It's okay!
There's plenty of demand for that!
Demand for what?!
Huh? Is something wrong, Bell?
HINATA!
Hinata— no... Hinata-chan!
Your big sister's about to take you
someplace lots of fun!
Don't worry, I promise I'll be gentle!
Wh-What are you doing, Bell?!
Mochida, make her stop!
Sorry, I'm on Bell's side.
Let's have a photoshoot later, Sunohara.
Seriously?!
Thank you for your patience.
As of now, the 22nd SunComi Expo
has officially begun.
You guys, the event's starting!
C'mon, clap!
New Comic
¥500
Maybe I made too many...
Sakura? What's the matter?
I-It's nothing! We've got this!
One comic, please!
Thank you very much! Here you go.
Is it okay if I take a look?
Of course! Go ahead!
I'll take it!
Th-Thanks for your support!
I sold one... Yes!
Y'mind if I flip through it?
Sure, go ahead!
The end of the line is here!
The vendors at this booth
are on a whole other level.
Whew, I'm beat!
Looks like the rush is finally dying down.
New Comic ¥500
I've never had this many people
visit my booth before.
It's all thanks to you guys!
I wouldn't say that.
No, it's the truth!
I mean, they hardly ever have
cosplayers of this caliber!
Sunohara looks downright adorable, too!
It's a popular genre for sure, but getting
this much business with an original comic?
I swear, it's practically a miracle—
S-Sorry! I got excited again...
It's fine. Don't apologize.
I'm just glad you're having fun.
I've thought this ever since we first met,
but you're passionate about
the things you love.
You pour your heart into them.
That's what I like the most about you, Sakura.
Th-Thank you.
Until now, I never had any friends who
I could talk to about these types of hobbies...
I'm having a blast today!
Excuse me.
You're Miss Sakura, right?
Y-Yes.
If you don't mind, could I get
a sketch request from you?
Sure, I'd be happy to!
Th-Thank you so much!
You two can take a break for now, okay?
Wearing these outfits brings back memories of
the adventure we went on in the other world.
Yeah, it does.
Traveling around a bunch of places...
Fighting demons...
Finally defeating the Demon Lord...
You and I, uniting as one...
That never happened!
I'm just glad we were able to make
everyone in the other world smile again.
The people in this world also seem happy.
Which is why the two of us
have a right to be happy, too.
Let's take our relationship to the next level!
Bell? Hey—!
Ah!
It might've torn because
you were squirming so much!
What?!
Stay still. We don't want anyone to see us.
No one's going to get in our way this time.
Hinata... It's high time that you and I—
Hey, you guys!
I hate to ask, but can you help me out?
O-Our bad!
Apologies for the wait!
Thanks for your support!